- Who the hell are you? - I'm Milo Walker. Who are you?
-你又是哪位 -我是迈洛 沃克  你是谁
Milo?
迈洛
What on earth? What...?
什么情况  怎么…
- What the...? - Oh, my.
-什么鬼…   -我的天
Wait a minute.
先等一下
Oh, Lord.
老天啊
- This isn't happening. - Pardon me?
-这不可能 -抱歉
- Who are you? - You're Spencer's grandfather.
-你是谁 -你是斯潘瑟的外公
- Yeah, no kidding. - And you are Milo.
-对 不骗你 -而你是迈洛
I certainly am.
我当然是
I'm Martha, Spencer's...
我是玛莎  斯潘瑟的…
You're the little girlfriend?
你是他的小女朋友
- Look out! - What?
-小心   -什么
- Ah! Oh, oh! - Oh, Lord.
-啊 噢 -哦 天哪
That hurt like a goddamn...
真是痛死我了
- Bethany? - What? I'm not...
-贝瑟妮 -什么  我不是
No.
不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no...
不  不  不
Yo!
啊
Oh, no, no, no. This can't be happening!
不  不  不  怎么会这样
Fridge?
冰箱
Yes, I'm Fridge, goddamn it!
是的  我是冰箱  见鬼了
The hell, man?
开什么玩笑
Okay. Okay, something went wrong.
好吧 看来什么情况不对
You think?
你说呢